Guide to the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers District Lodge 751 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- INTERNATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF MACHINISTS AND AEROSPACE WORKERS DISTRICT LODGE No. 751, 1937-2017; RECORD GROUP 1
  - PRESS AND PUBLICITY RECORDS, 1937-2009; SERIES 7 (Box-folder 9/10 - 10/13, OS, 12/19 - 13/6)
    - Contract negotiations and flyers, 2002 (Box-folder 10/1)
    - Contract negotiations, flyers, and organization, 2002 (Box-folder 10/2)
    - Contract flyers and pins/badges, 2002 (Box-folder 10/3)
    - Washington Machinists Council 75th anniversary dinner, 1963 (Box-folder 10/4)
    - Ed Springer news clippings (part 1 of 2), 1959-1965 (Box-folder 10/5)
    - Ed Springer news clippings (part 2 of 2), 1959-1965 (Box-folder 10/6)
    - The earth-orbiting flight of astronaut Scott Carpenter, 1962 (Box-folder 10/7)
    - Contract negotiations coverage, 1962 (Box-folder 10/8)
    - Elmer Walker / Albert Hayes commemorative booklet, 1965 (Box-folder 10/9)
    - Edwin Springer photographs, 1960s (Box-folder 10/10)
    - Union leaders meetings photographs, 1954-1964 (Box-folder 10/11)
    - NASA photographs of renderings of moon landing, 1963 (Box-folder 10/12)
    - Shaefer/Machinists Union Racing Team flyer, c. 1980s (Box-folder 10/13)
    - Aeronautical Mechanics Labor Day floats - photographs, 1937, 1940s (Box-folder 24/1)
    - Fighting Machinists on the Line for 69 - 1995 strike scrapbook, c. 1996 (Box-folder 24/2)
    - Press Scrapbook: Fighting Machinists On The Line In '89, c. 1990 (Box-folder 24/3)
    - Community film Union/GAV, undated(?) (Box-folder 26/1)
    - IAM/Union Lodge 751 Orientation, undated(?) (Box-folder 26/2)
    - You are not alone, undated(?) (Box-folder 26/3)
    - Switch-off Seafirst, c. 1981 (Box-folder 26/4)
    - No road too long, undated (?) (Box-folder 26/5)
    - IAM Grand Lodge. Stop subcontracting, 1992 (Box-folder 12/19)
    - IAM Grand Lodge. Dream stealer, undated (Box-folder 12/20)
    - IAM Grand Lodge. New member, undated (Box-folder 12/21)
    - IAM Grand Lodge videos (copies) (part 1 of 2), 2007-2009 (Box-folder 12/22)
    - IAM Grand Lodge videos (copies) (part 2 of 2), undated (Box-folder 12/23)
    - IAM Grand Lodge. Employee Free Choice Act, 2009 (Box-folder 12/24)
    - IAM Grand Lodge. Highlights from the 37th Grand Lodge convention, 2008 (Box-folder 12/25)
    - IAM Grand Lodge. W is Wrong, 2005 (Box-folder 12/26)
    - IAM Women's Department. Fighting for equality, 2007 (Box-folder 12/27)
    - IAM Grand Lodge. Legislative and political action, 2009 (Box-folder 12/28)
    - IAM Grand Lodge. IAM HPWO Partnerships and the Service Contract Act, 2008 (Box-folder 12/29)
    - 1983 Torchlight Parade Aero Float #240 (Box-folder 13/1)
    - Organizing, undated (Box-folder 13/2)
    - BEGNF / IAM Meeting 82, 1982 (Box-folder 13/3)
    - Adapt or Die, undated (Box-folder 13/4)
    - Placid Harbor, undated (Box-folder 13/5)
    - People for the American Way. Life and liberty for all who believe, c. 1980s (Box-folder 13/6)
  - PUBLICATIONS, 1941-2001; SERIES 8 (Box-folder 10/14 - 10/41)
    - IAM constitutions, 1942, 1977 (Box-folder 10/14)
    - IAM pamphlets, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 10/15)
    - Labor relations agreement with Boeing ,1940-1942: pamphlet, c. 1941 (Box-folder 10/16)
    - Machinists Non-partisan Political League materials, 1978 (Box-folder 10/17)
    - Who's fighting for me? Machinists Non Partisan Political League, 1992 (Box-folder 10/18)
    - Machinists Non Partisan Political League. Now let's get to work, 1993 (Box-folder 10/19)
    - IAM/Boeing Health and Safety Institute, 1991 (Box-folder 10/20)
    - IAM/Boeing Health and Safety Institute annual reports, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 10/21)
    - IAM/Boeing Joint Programs annual reports, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 10/22)
    - Jobs security prosperity: a steward's action guide, c. 1998 (Box-folder 10/23)
    - IAM Officers Guide, undated (Box-folder 10/24)
    - AFL-CIO. The changing situation of workers and their unions, 1985 (Box-folder 10/25)
    - Boeing Commercial Airplanes. Employee annual report, 1989 (Box-folder 10/26)
    - Union Steward's Role brochure, undated (Box-folder 10/27)
    - Organizing Committee Handbook, undated (Box-folder 10/28)
    - IAM. Pocket guide for shop stewards, undated (Box-folder 10/29)
    - 1978 Machinists Leadership Schools (Box-folder 10/30)
    - Western State Conference of Machinists. Proceedings, 1978 (Box-folder 10/31)
    - Boeing Magazine 50th anniversary issue, 1966 (Box-folder 10/1)
    - IAM/Boeing Quality Through Training annual reports, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 10/1)
    - IAM/Boeing Health and Safety Institute review of 1990 (Box-folder 10/1)
    - IAM/Boeing Quality Through Training Program reference guide, undated (Box-folder 10/1)
    - Boeing shareholder meeting agendas, 1993-2001 (Box-folder 10/1)
    - Wintergreen Symposium report, 1986 (Box-folder 10/1)
    - Aerospace Industry Training Partnership flyer, undated (Box-folder 10/1)
    - Aerospace Machinists District Lodge 751. Securing jobs today... for tomorrow, 1999 (Box-folder 10/1)
    - The Boeing Company hourly programs summary annual reports, 1976 (Box-folder 10/1)
    - Ritual of the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1972 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - ARTIFACTS, 1930s-2007; SERIES 9 (Box-folder 14/1 - 14/30; 16-23)
    - Badges and pins -- Boeing products, undated (Box-folder 14/1)
    - Badges and pins -- Machinists Non Partisan League, 1976-2005 (Box-folder 14/2)
    - Badges and pins -- electoral politics, 1972-2004 (Box-folder 14/3)
    - Badges and pins -- union elections, undated (Box-folder 14/4)
    - Badges and pins -- IAM District Lodge 751, undated (Box-folder 14/5)
    - Badges and pins -- IAM, undated (Box-folder 14/6)
    - Badges and pins -- women in union, undated (Box-folder 14/7)
    - Badges and pins -- negotiations and strikes, 1977-1992 (Box-folder 14/8)
    - Badges and pins -- negotiations and strikes, 1993-2002 (Box-folder 14/9)
    - Badges and pins -- shop committeeman and union steward, undated (Box-folder 14/10)
    - Badges and pins -- "buy American" and solidarity, undated (Box-folder 14/11)
    - Badges and pins -- other unions, undated (Box-folder 14/12)
    - Badges and pins -- safety and charitable, undated (Box-folder 14/13)
    - Coalition of Labor Union Women memorabilia, undated (Box-folder 14/14)
    - Jackie Boschok convention badges, 1986-2007 (Box-folder 14/15)
    - Coalition of Labor Union Women fanny pack, undated (Box-folder 14/16)
    - Coalition of Labor Union Women convention badges, c. 2000s (Box-folder 14/17)
    - Questep program items, 1991 (Box-folder 14/18)
    - Union steward journal (blank), undated (Box-folder 14/19)
    - IAM/Boeing Quality Through Training Program pens, undated (Box-folder 14/20)
    - Patches, badges, stickers, undated (Box-folder 14/21)
    - Patches, undated, 2012 (Box-folder 14/22)
    - 50th anniversary pencils, 1985 (Box-folder 14/23)
    - IAM/Boeing playing cards, undated (Box-folder 14/24)
    - IAM/Boeing joint program pens, undated (Box-folder 14/25)
    - Buy American bumper stickers, undated (Box-folder 14/26)
    - Member dues books, 1941-1977 (Box-folder 14/27)
    - Member artifacts, c. 1930s (Box-folder 14/28)
    - IAM/Boeing Quality Through Training Program mouse pad, undated (Box-folder 14/29)
    - IAM/Boeing joint program hand fan, undated (Box-folder 14/30)
    - Caps, 1980s-1990s (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Sweatshirts, 1980s-1990s (Box-folder 1/16)
    - Jackets (1 of 3), 1980s-1990s (Box-folder 1/17)
    - Jackets (2 of 3), 1980s-1990s (Box-folder 1/18)
    - Jackets (3 of 3), 1980s-1990s (Box-folder 1/19)
    - T-shirts (1 of 3), 1980s-1990s (Box-folder 1/20)
    - T-shirts (2 of 3), 1980s-1990s (Box-folder 1/21)
    - T-shirts (3 of 3), 1980s-1990s (Box-folder 1/22)
  - EPHEMERA, 1942-2017; SERIES 10 (Box-folder 15/1 - 15/10, OS)
    - Contact information and clock numbers (notebook), undated (Box-folder 15/1)
    - Paycheck and ID card copies, 1942-1953 (Box-folder 15/2)
    - Leroy Miller time book and certificates, 1958-1967 (Box-folder 15/3)
    - Negotiated wage rates card, 1973 (Box-folder 15/4)
    - Presidential advance training motorcade badge, 1998 (Box-folder 15/5)
    - Evellyn B Hanna memorabilia, 1957-1985 (Box-folder 15/6)
    - Unlabeled photographs, undated (Box-folder 15/7)
    - Boeing promotional photographs, undated (Box-folder 15/8)
    - Certificates, 1982, 2013 (Box-folder 15/9)
    - Gold Sponsor Certificate for PNAA Scholarship Program, 2013 (Box-folder 15/10)
    - Commemorative posters, 1988-2017 (Box-folder Oversized)
- WASHINGTON MACHINISTS COUNCIL, 1977-1980; RECORD GROUP 2 (Box-folder 24/1 - 24/6)
  - Minutes, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 25/1)
  - Minutes and financial reports May - November, 1980 (Box-folder 25/2)
  - Minutes, endorsements, and fund contributions, 1980 (Box-folder 25/3)
  - Notifications, financial reports and trustee correspondence, 1980 (Box-folder 25/4)
  - Committee minutes, 1980 (Box-folder 25/5)
  - Gerry Dargitz' file with Washington Machinist Council, Washington State Labor Council, political - notes and correspondence, 1980 (Box-folder 25/6)